NGUYEN NHUT TRINH

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

01656 033 621

0356 033 621

SKYPE: MRNHUTTRINH

MRNHUTTRINH@GMAIL.COM

WWW.GITHUB.COM/MRNHUTTRINH

BRIEF PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

REACTJS (redux-saga, redux-thunk)

ANGULARJS

VUEJS

REACT-NATIVE

JAVASCRIPT/ES6

TYPESCRIPT

HTML5/CSS3

SCSS/SASS

WEBPACK/BABEL

UX/UI

OOP

NODE JS

JAVA

PYTHON

POSTGRES

REDSHIFT

SQL SERVER

ENGLISH

MANAGEMENT

ANALYSIS

SOCIAL MEDIA

TWITTER: @MRNHUTTRINH FACEBOOK: /MRNHUTTRINH

PROFILE

Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. As an ambitious and hard-working individual, I handle multiple tasks on a daily basis competently, working well under the pressure. More than 4 years working on online industry as a web developer, I've learned & got experiences at web development environments, program languages, database, and management operation system. I'm confident in my ability to come up with interesting ideas for project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Positioin: 70% Frontend - 30% Backend

FREELANCE TEAM | OCT 2017 - JUN 2018 (2 PROJECTS)

- Analyze requirements, research and develop new features.
- Design new features base on exist structure system.
- Design mockup, database schema and write specification document for team members do their works.
- Develop web application with JAVA, Javascript, ReactJs and Material UI
- Develop RESTful API providing JSON data format for mobile and web application.
- Exploit web system
- Tracking performance, improve connection speed, customize sql statement to improve query database performance
- Co-worker, support team member when they're getting stuck.

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Positioin: 70% Frontend - 30% Backend

TMA SOLUTIONS | JAN 2015 - PRESENT (+4 PROJECTS)

- Analyze requirements, research and develop new features.
- Develop web application with JAVA, NodeJS, Websocket, ExpressJS, Jesmine, Babel, Springboot, Python, Javascript, Typescript, ReactJs and Material UI, Bootstrap, Jquery, Postgres, RedShift.
- Research and develop new components/company coding library using new technologies
- Assist Team Leader to estimate development related tasks, design the database schema and identify risks
- Provide support to Software Development Engineer to maintain and extend existing development software and activities
- Support to create test plans and scripts, carry out bugs testing, identify defects and fix them where they were discovered or required.
- Develop RESTful API providing JSON data format for mobile and web application.
- Co-worker, support team member when they're getting stuck.

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Positioin: 70% Frontend - 30% Backend
KIEN NHAN JSC | JUL 2013 - DEC 2014 (2 PROJECTS)

- Analyze requirements, research and develop new features.
- Develop web application with .NET, MVC5 , SignalR, Javascript, AngularJS, Bootstrap, Jquery, SQLSERVER.
- Co-worker, support team member when they're getting stuck.

SKILLS

OBJECT-ORIENTED PROGRAMMING (OOP) 4/5

FRONT END 4/5

JAVASCRIPT (ES5, ES6, COMMONJS, REQUIREJS)
TYPESCRIPT
HTML5/CSS3/SCSS
WEBPACK, GULP, GRUNT, BABEL
SOCKETIO, WEBSOCKET
JQUERY, REACTJS, REDUX, ANGULAR, VUEJS
UI DESIGN: BOOTSTRAP, PURE CSS, MATERIAL UI, FLAT UI

BACK END 4/5

JAVA (CORE, SPRING BOOT)
ASP.NET (MVC)
NODEJS
PYTHON

DATABASE 4/5

POSTGRES, REDSHIFT, MYSQL, SQL SERVER

COMMUNICATION INTERMEDIATE

ENGLISH

OTHER SKILL 4/5

LEAD ANALYTIC

EDUCATION

OPEN UNIVERSITY | 2009 - 2013 COMPUTER SCIENTIST